ウボォーのその後は 知らなかったけど
Well... Instead of my left arm...
鎖野郎の顔と名前は分かったわ。 [TEL]　能力は　まだ不明。 分かった。
Is it all right if I bet the thing I usually bet? What?
ベーチタクルホテルの ロビーで待つ。
What do you bet? My life.
残りの仲間は３人…　行こう。
It appears I was the one lacking in resolve!
パクノダをさらっても 意味がない
So this is it?
俺がクラピカなら ターゲットを変更する
Our golden opportunity? Yes...
どの道　「旅団」をつぶすなら 狙うのは　頭だ
Our chance to infiltrate the palace.
てめぇ！
These strange trees bear very large fruit.
今　何時だと思ってんだ！ ん？ バカ！ ベーチタクルホテルだよ。
Around five hundred per tree...
何度　聞き間違いすりゃ 気が済むんだ　あぁ？
And there are ten trees. A total of five thousand.
レオリオ
Five hundred thousand people were to undergo
ん？　何見てんだ　こら！　あぁ？ 消します？ ほっとけ　目を合わすな。
the selection process each day,
with a one-percent survival rate.
あ？　見せもんじゃねえぞ　あぁ？ ったく 間抜けな手下　持ったおかげで
But thanks to Killua's distractions,
that schedule was only fulfilled on one day, so the numbers add up...
俺のお先　真っ暗だぜ。 いいか？ 目ぇつぶるのは今回だけだ。
These are cocoons holding the
humans who were selected.
次　ヘマしたら分かってんな？ よく聞けよ　７時きっかりだ！ それまでにホテルに来い！
Which means they will become Nen-wielding
human weapons at the King's disposal, turning against the rest of humanity.
メッセージだ
Neferpitou is probably a Manipulator...
７時きっかり 闇に乗じること はぁ。 関節を外して 瞬時に糸から抜け出し
and intends to manipulate these
soldiers per the King's will, expanding his conquest throughout the world.
攻撃するまで０．７秒前後
I will not let that happen!
余裕でいける 奴らだって突然　停電すれば 闇に目が慣れるまで 数秒は　かかる
First, the far exit... is set. Next...
さて　最後の曲は
I must get closer.
ペンネーム　キッチョムさんからの リクエストです。
The palace entrance looks dark...
パク達が来た。 おっ？
So far, so good...
ハハ　分かったぜ。 結局　気が変わって 入団したくなったんだろ？
Middle exit... set.
あんた達に懸けられてた賞金が 取り消しになったこと 知らなかっただけだよ。
Now for the near exit.
その結果　また尾行に 失敗したのか？　懲りねえな。
There aren't any guards...
だが これも何かの縁ってやつよ。 あと２分
I'd imagine only a select few are inside.
まっ　仲良くやろうぜ。
This will work.
ヤダね　懸賞金があったからこそ 追っかけてたんだ。
If I've come this far,
I can reach the inner palace.
本当なら　お前らなんか 顔も見たくないんだからな。
The throne room is on the third
floor, at the rear and center.
うまい　これなら目をつむっても 不自然じゃ　ない
We must delay any reinforcements,
even if by only a second.
俺もだね。 ヘヘヘ。
The first floor is too far for that.
どうだい？　団長　いいタマだろ？
The central stairway, second floor.
ウボォーに通じる ふてぶてしさがある。
That's the best location!
それより鎖野郎って　どんな奴？ その前に　パク もう一度　こいつら調べろ。
The central stairway is beyond this courtyard...
俺達は　何も隠してないし 何も知らな…。
To be safe, I'll leave an exit here...
やれば分かること　黙りなさい。 もし知ってても　別のこと考えて
No, that would be no different
from the one outside... It should at least
頭の中　読ませないも…。
be next to the first floor's central stairway.
フッ…　そういうこと。 何か勘違いしてるわね。
Then, if I can, I'll go up from
there to the second floor...
私の質問で あんた達の記憶を刺激する。
Window Opener
Scream
すると 池に石を投げた時みたいに
Scream...
記憶の底で沈殿した泥が舞う。
Close!
見える！　奴らは見えていない
Are any others around? If I'm seen, it's over.
右の奴が抜けた？ 見えない これを　たくらんでたのか！
I'll have to retreat...
糸を切るには　殺るしかない！
Nothing's coming?
パク　平気？ 左手と奥歯を折られたわ。 ちょっと見くびってたね。
This is it. I can't move beyond this point...
それより　びっくりよ。
If I do, I'll be killed.
その子達…。 待て！
What is that aura?
パクノダ…　おめぇにだ。
It appears to be full of all
kinds of misfortune...
おい　一体　どうなってるんだ？
What I fear is that, before killing me, the monsters up there
ホテルの受付嬢に変装して… ノーマーク
will squeeze every drop of information
from me that I have on the King...
いや　それよりも　この事実 あの位置からの鎖の攻撃は 団長なら十分に回避できる
Using any brutal means necessary.
しかし　不意の暗黒
If I'm caught, I won't be able to resist...
一瞬のロスが 鎖への反応を遅らせた
The aura's strength just confirms it...
初めから狙われていた 周到な準備
This is as far as I go...
秘密主義の上に　基本は冷徹 これは脅しではないと 考えたほうがいい
Oh, aren't you that lion guy from TV?
あの闇の中 数秒のロスを覚悟してまで
My name is Leol, and don't forget it.
メッセージを残した意味…
I heard that I should expect
a crayfish and wolf.
それは　このメッセージが 真実だから 奴には 心臓の鼓動を聞くことで
They're dealing with the grunts you created. So I can fight you one-on-one.
他人の感情を読み取れる 仲間がいる
I appreciate that.
そいつがいるからこそ 奴が残したメッセージ 私が話せば
This guy's just as strong as Cheetu.
奴は　仲間を見殺しにしてでも 団長を殺すだろう
No, he's a little stronger. Let's get started.
裏を返せば　まだ　この２人には 人質としての 価値があるということ パク。
Right now, allowing Knov to get
into the palace is the priority.
それは団長を奪還するチャンス パク。 だけど… パク！
Until that happens, I need to
divert the enemy's attention.
これから　おめぇは ひと言も話すな。
That won't help.
この２人から引き出した 鎖野郎の能力と　その弱点
This is Marcos. Do you have the meat?
これを今　みんなに話せば 奴は倒せる　造作もなく…
Yes, as requested.
でも　それには団長の死が 高い確率で　つきまとう
Refrigerated trucks are entering
the underground warehouse...
恐らく　ウボォーが そうだったように 「クモ」のための死
They're shipping in food.
団長の占いは どうだったのだろう 「２択」…
If the information Marcos
provided was accurate, living women are also inside.
話すのが裏切りなのか だますのが裏切りなのか
Not for the King, but for the
lecherous Secretary Bizeff.
) そうね　考え過ぎてるわ
If everything is going as planned, Palm should be inside.
フィンクス　急げ！ 団長が　さらわれた。
Leave the fourth truck as it is.
団長…
Yes, sir.
私達には まだ　あなたが必要です
Then we'll be leaving.
つまり　この状態は 予言するほどのこともない
Area D, of the underground warehouse.
取るに足らない 出来事というわけだ。 貴様…！ クラピカ！
My very own paradise, where no one can interfere.
五分？ お前も　とんだピント外れだな。
Now, please step out.
前提が　まず間違っているよ。
There's nothing to worry about.
追い詰められているのは お前達のほうだ。
From now on, you will work here.
どういうことだ？ 彼の心臓は　至って平常。
I've prepared rooms for each of you.
動揺は　みじんもないの。
You will be provided with all necessities.
死への不安　恐怖　何もないわ。
In your spare time, you may do as you want.
死を受け入れている音 死を毎日　そばにあるものとして 享受している音。
As long as you don't attempt to escape.
何で　こんな音が出せるの？
Your only job
もうイヤ！　もう聞きたくない その人の音も　あなたの音も。
is to follow my orders.
センリツ…。 彼は　本当に自分には 人質の価値がないと思っている。
When summoned, you must drop everything, and come to see me at once.
でも　彼が リーダーだということも事実。
Yes, Mr. Secretary. Excellent.
停電したの。 その隙に団長が　さらわれた。
You...
鎖野郎からのメッセージが これ。
Come with me. Yes.
奴には　プロハンタークラスの 仲間が　まだ　いる。 で？
The rest of you can wait in your rooms.
メッセージの裏を　よく読め！
Yes...
こいつらには 人質の価値があるって証しだ。
The Secretary was...
下手に動いて　こいつらに 逃げられたらアウトなんだぞ。
...interested in us!
恐らく？ 言ったろうが　停電！ 目が慣れた時には 団長は　もう　いなかった。
I must find a way out of here, so I can see the King and his Royal Guard.
とにかく 動ける状態じゃなかったんだ！ ＯＫ　反省会は後。
Using her crystal ball, Palm can observe
とにかく対策だ。
the current whereabouts of
anyone she has seen previously.
５年ほど前　緋の眼のクルタ族を 虐殺した時 すでに　お前は リーダーだったのか？
This power will allow her to keep tabs
on the King and Royal Guard.
答えろ！
The Hunters will then be able to determine
それが　ウボォーを殺した鎖か。
the optimal route for the operation. Only one exit.
ウボォーは 最後に何と言っていた？
I'll have to manipulate Bizeff.
覚えていないな。
My mission is crucial for
increasing our chances
ウソだな　だろ？　お仲間さん。
of defeating the King!
気持は分かる　俺も同じだ お前に話すことなど　何もない。
What matters most isn't that I succeed...
クラピカ　挑発だ　乗るな！ クソ…　クソ…
But that, should I fail and be captured,
I kill myself immediately.
団長からだ。 えっ？ もしもし。
I should be safe here...
従わなければ　即座に お前らのリーダーは殺す。
Palm...
１つ　追跡は　するな。
Don't do anything foolish!
２つ 人質の２人に危害を加えるな。 [TEL]　３つ パクノダという女に代われ。 その前に　１つ　いいか？ ２つ目の指示だが
I managed to place the exits, so even if your mission doesn't succeed,
we can still execute the operation. If you get caught, it's over...
人質の２人は　さっき暴れた時に 何か所か　骨折させちまった。
That... That...
フッ。
That vicious aura...
ならば　交渉の余地はない。 [TEL]
One look was all it took
すまん　ウソだ　２人は無傷だ。
to break my will...
次は　ないぞ くだらんまねは　するな。 さっさと　パクノダに代われ。
Gon... Killua...
痛っ！ もしもし。 [TEL]　まず　この会話を聞くのは お前１人だ。
You must have seen that aura...
[TEL]　離れた場所に移れ。 チッ。
You were probably even closer,
actually touching it...
[TEL]　スクワラという男と接触したか？ ええ。 [TEL]　では　センリツという女のことは？ 知ってるわ。
Yet...
[TEL]　ならば　話は早い。
How are you still able
[TEL]　よく聞け　まず　今から仲間との コミュニケーションを禁ずる。
to face them?
会話はもちろん　動作　筆記　暗号 アイコンタクト　その他一切だ。
How can you bring yourself to fight? Is it to save your friends?
これから場所を指示するが お前１人で来い。
To protect humanity? Why...
[TEL]　その時　わずかでも 鼓動に動揺があれば
Why are you still fighting?
人質は殺す　分かったな。
Palm!
一度　代われ さっきの男以外の奴だ。
Please...
代わったぜ。 [TEL]　これから　パクノダ１人と会う。
Don't do anything foolish. I beg you...
[TEL]　残りの者は　全員アジトに戻れ １０人　常に同じ場所にいろ。
If you're caught, it's all over...
[TEL]　１人でも欠けていたら 人質は殺す。
Palm!
[TEL]　いいな。 ああ。
I won't be able...
[TEL]　もう一度　パクノダと代われ。 ほれ。
to go back there...
迷うな　パクノダ みんなと来い こいつは使命より仲間をとる
I brought you something cold to drink.
鎖野郎の指示だ。 それが　どうした。
You're dismissed.
指示に背いたら 団長が殺られるんだぞ！
Wait in your room. Yes.
ここでパクノダを追跡するのは 必須　絶対条件だ。
Your lack of familiarity with the
area has sealed your defeat.
同感だな　パク１人だけ行かせても 意味がない。 ズルズル　奴の指示に従えば 占い通りになっちゃうよ。
Though it's almost too perfect that,
after all that running, you ended up in an underground church.
私は　ノブナガに賛成だ　今は　まだ 指示に従ったほうがいい。
In case of emergency, this place
is used as an air shelter.
僕も。 「今は」？　そりゃ　いつまでだ？
An ideal place to die in a vain struggle.
手足が半分なくなるまでか？ ケッ。
Well, you'll have to say your own prayers.
シズク　お前は？ っていうか もめたらコインでしょ？
I'm an atheist. You're a cocky guy.
ん　でも やっぱりノブナガ派かな。 団長には　まだ死んでほしくないし もちろん　パクもだけど。
Let's see who's trapped whom.
今すぐ ぶっ殺したいところだが
Cheetu told me everything.
パクノダを追うのが先だ。 待て！
I hear you can mold that
smoke into various objects.
そこから一歩でも進んだら斬るぜ。 ほぉ　やってみろよ。
Even better. If he believes things are going his way, he won't hesitate to display his abilities.
団員同士のマジギレ禁止。
However, I've yet to meet anyone whose power
お前 ノブナガ派じゃなかったのか？ 心情的にはね でも　ルールは絶対。
allows them to react more
flexibly than Deep Purple.
ルールの否定は　「クモ」の否定 それは　団長をも否定する。
I can feel the tension in the air... I love it.
それだけは　したくないから。
Both of us waiting to reveal our abilities...
[TEL] 奴からだ。
I really dig it.
俺が出よう。 もし…。 [TEL]　人質のどちらかを出せ。
It's common sense to defeat an opponent
before they can use their power.
この…。
But that isn't how men
ほら。
should fight.
余計なこと言うんじゃねえ もしもし。
Hey, what are you up to?
[TEL]　３０分以内にアジトに戻れ。
Voluntarily removing one of your senses?
小細工を　いくらしても構わないが リーダーが死ぬだけだ。
Have you heard of the band Black Planet?
またすぐ連絡する。 [TEL]
Their second album is super cool.
これじゃ　追跡は無理だね。 クソが！
It's a twelve-song medley.
１０人揃ってねえと 団長が死ぬか。
Listening to the whole thing's
like reading a good book.
人質を連絡係に 使うとはな　頭のいい野郎だ。
When you finish it, you feel great. I know.
団長と戦うチャンスだが 僕が　ここをふければ団長が死ぬ というわけなんだ
And best part of all, the medley's
exactly sixty minutes long.
助けてくれ
It's a masterpiece!
いいよ　クロロより ちょっとだけ付き合い長いしね。
I hate to admit it, but I agree.
クラピカの執念が実を結び 「旅団」との対決は ついに最終局面を迎える
Rental, start! This could be bad...